Alvi Rahman

929-302-5036 | rahman.alvi2002@gmail.com | New York City, NY 10472 | LinkedIn

Summary

Specialized in collaborative work with a background in coordinating and developing various projects. Committed to accomplishing tasks and projects all the way through. A dynamic mindset that is willing to branch out into various fields.

Education

Hunter College, 695 Park Ave, New York, NY 10065 B.S Degree in Computer Science (expected by June 2024) Current GPA: 3.5 September 2020 - Current

Experience

Coding League, The Brooklyn Latin School

September 2018 - March 2020

- Chaired projects with small groups of 3-4 individuals.
- Collaborated with team members and advisors to complete goals.
- Promoted events to garner more attention from the community.
- Assisted individuals in developing their skills.
- Communicated and interacted with various personalities to adapt methods of assistance.
- Committed for 6 hours a week to practice and develop projects.
- Utilized JavaScript, HTML, and CSS to create web-browser games and websites.

Sales Associate, ZARA June 2021-August 2021

- Assisted in carrying out sales for the business.
- Communicated with customers and managers to effectively carry out their needs.
- Organized and sorted through articles of clothing.
- Memorized prices, layouts, and customs quickly for efficiency.
- Cooperated with fellow employees to operate at peak performance.

Private Freelance Tutor

- Taken requests from various individuals in assisting with many STEM related needs.
- Dedicated hours for students during school.
- Assisted with Calculus, **Python**, and **C++** assignments.
- Refined my personal understanding of subjects in order to teach them skillfully.

Relevant Courses

Discrete Mathematics, Software Analysis and Design, Calculus II

Skills

Computer: Excel, PowerPoint, Word, Adobe Photoshop, Social Media, Digital Art

Programming: Intermediate in Python and C++. JavaScript, CSS, HTML, Chrome Extensions, SQL

Language: Fluency in Bangla